const level20questions = [
     
 {
    question: "6 + 10 / 2 - 9 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "-16", "-10", "-11"],
    answer: "-16",
},
{
    question: "8 + 3 x 4 - 10 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["8", "15", "46", "10"],
    answer: "15",
},
{
    question: "5 + 10 - 7 x 6 / 6 = ?",
    options: ["-13", "8", "12", "-10"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "1 - 8 x 3 + 6 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["-52", "-21", "-15", "-56"],
    answer: "-15",
},
{
    question: "3 / 1 + 1 x 4 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["3", "2", "40", "5"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "6 / 2 x 4 - 1 + 10 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "21", "16", "11"],
    answer: "16",
},
{
    question: "6 x 8 - 3 / 1 + 7 = ?",
    options: ["35", "52", "28", "4"],
    answer: "52",
},
{
    question: "2 - 10 / 1 + 2 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["-4", "96", "1", "17"],
    answer: "-4",
},
{
    question: "2 / 1 - 7 + 2 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["-3", "45", "39", "4"],
    answer: "-3",
},
{
    question: "4 + 6 x 1 - 6 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["8", "29", "30", "9"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "6 x 4 / 2 + 4 - 2 = ?",
    options: ["-2", "28", "14", "25"],
    answer: "14",
},
{
    question: "8 x 3 - 4 + 8 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["18", "17", "24", "90"],
    answer: "17",
},
{
    question: "5 - 7 / 7 x 8 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["1", "-6", "4", "-2"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "8 - 5 x 3 + 9 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["-10", "-4", "7", "-42"],
    answer: "-10",
},
{
    question: "2 - 4 + 9 x 9 / 9 = ?",
    options: ["8", "19", "7", "16"],
    answer: "16",
},
{
    question: "10 + 1 - 7 x 5 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["6", "-24", "-1", "-36"],
    answer: "-36",
},
{
    question: "3 x 7 + 6 / 6 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["40", "0", "12", "81"],
    answer: "0",
},
{
    question: "8 + 5 x 5 - 2 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["79", "50", "-4", "32"],
    answer: "50",
},
{
    question: "2 - 10 / 1 + 4 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["12", "13", "43", "16"],
    answer: "12",
},
{
    question: "10 / 5 x 4 + 7 - 8 = ?",
    options: ["5", "3", "19", "7"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "3 + 6 / 3 - 3 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["-52", "-30", "2", "-20"],
    answer: "2",
},
{
    question: "5 x 6 + 4 - 5 / 5 = ?",
    options: ["33", "44", "7", "58"],
    answer: "33",
},
{
    question: "3 / 1 x 6 + 5 - 4 = ?",
    options: ["9", "19", "70", "27"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "7 + 2 - 8 x 9 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["-27", "6", "-34", "7"],
    answer: "7",
},
{
    question: "8 x 6 - 9 / 3 + 7 = ?",
    options: ["11", "33", "78", "52"],
    answer: "33",
}, {
    question: "1 - 7 / 1 x 3 + 9 = ?",
    options: ["1", "-11", "-77", "-23"],
    answer: "-11",
},
{
    question: "10 x 3 / 3 - 4 + 8 = ?",
    options: ["16", "15", "35", "14"],
    answer: "15",
},
{
    question: "1 + 10 x 9 - 3 / 3 = ?",
    options: ["28", "54", "62", "90"],
    answer: "28",
},
{
    question: "8 + 3 x 3 - 5 / 5 = ?",
    options: ["66", "16", "-1", "29"],
    answer: "16",
},
{
    question: "10 x 6 / 4 + 5 - 5 = ?",
    options: ["26", "15", "23", "5"],
    answer: "15",
},
{
    question: "8 + 3 - 7 x 4 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["-28", "4", "-3", "16"],
    answer: "4",
},
{
    question: "3 - 5 x 6 / 3 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["-24", "-1", "-37", "-20"],
    answer: "-1",
},
{
    question: "7 - 9 + 8 / 1 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["20", "12", "27", "38"],
    answer: "20",
},
{
    question: "8 x 2 - 9 + 10 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["12", "72", "40", "17"],
    answer: "17",
},
{
    question: "6 x 2 / 4 - 1 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["7", "3", "87", "8"],
    answer: "8",
},
{
    question: "9 / 1 - 2 x 2 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["-13", "9", "6", "-5"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "3 - 1 x 9 / 3 + 6 = ?",
    options: ["-27", "6", "10", "-6"],
    answer: "10",
},
{
    question: "7 x 3 - 8 / 1 + 2 = ?",
    options: ["56", "11", "44", "15"],
    answer: "15",
},
{
    question: "5 - 3 x 5 / 1 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["-32", "12", "-6", "3"],
    answer: "3",
},
{
    question: "4 - 6 + 8 / 1 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["8", "21", "38", "20"],
    answer: "20",
},
{
    question: "6 / 4 x 10 + 1 - 9 = ?",
    options: ["24", "7", "3", "59"],
    answer: "7",
},
{
    question: "2 + 10 / 2 x 7 - 3 = ?",
    options: ["37", "-4", "34", "8"],
    answer: "34",
},
{
    question: "5 x 3 + 3 / 3 - 7 = ?",
    options: ["31", "29", "10", "9"],
    answer: "9",
},
{
    question: "6 + 10 x 1 - 10 / 2 = ?",
    options: ["20", "11", "28", "19"],
    answer: "11",
},
{
    question: "10 / 5 + 7 x 5 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["81", "1", "11", "27"],
    answer: "27",
},
{
    question: "3 / 8 x 8 + 5 - 7 = ?",
    options: ["15", "1", "16", "7"],
    answer: "1",
},
{
    question: "5 + 9 / 9 - 3 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["0", "-10", "-30", "4"],
    answer: "0",
},
{
    question: "1 / 1 x 10 + 10 - 7 = ?",
    options: ["13", "4", "-6", "7"],
    answer: "13",
},
{
    question: "6 + 1 - 8 x 5 / 1 = ?",
    options: ["-33", "4", "7", "-9"],
    answer: "7",
},
{
    question: "4 / 4 + 3 x 6 - 6 = ?",
    options: ["16", "28", "9", "13"],
    answer: "13",
}, {
question: "6 / 6 x 10 - 8 + 4 = ?",
options: ["9", "2", "5", "6"],
answer: "9"
},
{
question: "6 + 2 / 1 - 2 x 10 = ?",
options: ["-12", "-7", "-25", "-67"],
answer: "-12"
},
{
question: "5 + 4 - 2 / 2 x 8 = ?",
options: ["11", "1", "9", "14"],
answer: "9"
},
{
question: "5 x 4 + 3 / 1 - 5 = ?",
options: ["43", "7", "18", "61"],
answer: "18"
},
{
question: "6 / 3 + 2 - 6 x 4 = ?",
options: ["-10", "-20", "-1", "-36"],
answer: "-1"
},
{
question: "9 / 9 + 8 - 10 x 9 = ?",
options: ["-81", "-13", "1", "-37"],
answer: "-81"
},
{
question: "8 - 10 x 10 + 4 / 2 = ?",
options: ["-37", "-45", "3", "-90"],
answer: "-37"
},
{
question: "2 + 2 / 2 - 9 x 7 = ?",
options: ["-12", "9", "-60", "-6"],
answer: "-60"
},
{
question: "1 - 9 + 9 x 6 / 9 = ?",
options: ["5", "2", "-5", "-2"],
answer: "-5"
},
{
question: "5 x 10 - 6 + 8 / 4 = ?",
options: ["17", "11", "46", "96"],
answer: "46"
},
{
question: "9 - 2 / 2 + 10 x 1 = ?",
options: ["48", "37", "18", "36"],
answer: "18"
},
{
question: "4 x 9 / 4 + 4 - 6 = ?",
options: ["28", "62", "7", "3"],
answer: "7"
},
{
question: "5 x 4 + 4 / 1 - 6 = ?",
options: ["88", "25", "18", "36"],
answer: "18"
},
{
question: "9 x 2 - 10 / 2 + 6 = ?",
options: ["81", "19", "23", "6"],
answer: "19"
},
{
question: "4 / 10 x 10 + 10 - 3 = ?",
options: ["26", "11", "-2", "40"],
answer: "11"
},
{
question: "8 / 1 + 2 - 9 x 8 = ?",
options: ["-16", "-61", "-8", "-62"],
answer: "-61"
},
{
question: "6 + 1 / 3 x 9 - 10 = ?",
options: ["5", "-1", "-5", "8"],
answer: "-5"
},
{
question: "2 - 10 / 2 + 8 x 5 = ?",
options: ["101", "19", "38", "37"],
answer: "37"
},
{
question: "4 x 1 / 1 + 3 - 9 = ?",
options: ["-2", "1", "4", "71"],
answer: "-2"
},
{
question: "2 x 1 + 6 / 6 - 4 = ?",
options: ["-1", "46", "19", "31"],
answer: "-1"
},
{
question: "8 x 3 / 8 + 3 - 7 = ?",
options: ["25", "16", "-1", "0"],
answer: "-1"
},
{
question: "10 x 9 + 1 - 1 / 1 = ?",
options: ["90", "47", "17", "44"],
answer: "90"
},
{
question: "3 x 8 / 8 + 10 - 9 = ?",
options: ["3", "6", "4", "9"],
answer: "4"
},
{
question: "2 + 5 - 6 x 2 / 6 = ?",
options: ["11", "5", "8", "-32"],
answer: "5"
},
{
question: "4 / 2 - 4 x 2 + 1 = ?",
options: ["-5", "-17", "-12", "-7"],
answer: "-5"
},

{
question: "1 x 4 - 6 + 6 / 6 = ?",
options: ["48", "-3", "-1", "8"],
answer: "-1"
},
{
question: "3 - 1 + 9 / 1 x 10 = ?",
options: ["18", "6", "9", "92"],
answer: "92"
},
{
question: "5 / 5 - 9 + 6 x 2 = ?",
options: ["39", "2", "4", "64"],
answer: "4"
},
{
question: "4 / 4 - 3 + 10 x 5 = ?",
options: ["5", "40", "48", "-1"],
answer: "5"
},
{
question: "8 x 1 - 10 / 2 + 9 = ?",
options: ["18", "15", "12", "4"],
answer: "12"
},
{
question: "9 / 3 x 1 + 2 - 3 = ?",
options: ["2", "14", "13", "36"],
answer: "2"
},
{
question: "9 + 7 - 5 / 1 x 1 = ?",
options: ["11", "9", "-1", "-38"],
answer: "11"
},
{
question: "3 / 6 x 6 + 2 - 2 = ?",
options: ["39", "6", "3", "-1"],
answer: "3"
},
{
question: "2 / 2 + 7 x 9 - 7 = ?",
options: ["13", "57", "12", "38"],
answer: "12"
},
{
question: "10 - 4 / 2 + 1 x 3 = ?",
options: ["78", "11", "21", "14"],
answer: "11"
},
{
question: "10 x 6 + 3 / 3 - 1 = ?",
options: ["60", "30", "46", "25"],
answer: "60"
},
{
question: "5 - 6 x 4 / 6 + 4 = ?",
options: ["6", "1", "5", "-14"],
answer: "6"
},
{
question: "9 / 1 + 3 - 7 x 7 = ?",
options: ["-37", "-11", "1", "-49"],
answer: "-37"
},
{
question: "5 - 10 + 4 x 10 / 5 = ?",
options: ["3", "21", "36", "7"],
answer: "3"
},
{
question: "9 + 6 / 6 - 3 x 1 = ?",
options: ["-22", "-12", "-46", "7"],
answer: "-12"
},
{
question: "8 / 1 + 10 x 10 - 9 = ?",
options: ["99", "29", "17", "76"],
answer: "99"
},
{
question: "9 - 1 x 1 + 4 / 4 = ?",
options: ["3", "-8", "-67", "9"],
answer: "9"
},
{
question: "10 + 7 - 4 / 4 x 2 = ?",
options: ["5", "15", "4", "17"],
answer: "5"
},
{
question: "9 / 9 - 7 x 4 + 5 = ?",
options: ["-64", "-22", "-10", "-3"],
answer: "-10"
},
{
question: "7 x 5 - 4 + 1 / 1 = ?",
options: ["44", "32", "7", "-1"],
answer: "32"
},
{
question: "5 + 10 - 5 x 7 / 5 = ?",
options: ["8", "-11", "-29", "7"],
answer: "8"
},
{
question: "1 + 10 - 6 x 8 / 8 = ?",
options: ["6", "-12", "5", "2"],
answer: "5"
},
{
question: "9 / 9 x 2 - 7 + 4 = ?",
options: ["14", "18", "24", "-1"],
answer: "-1"
},
{
question: "4 + 3 x 6 / 2 - 1 = ?",
options: ["-5", "3", "41", "12"],
answer: "3"
},
{
question: "7 + 3 x 9 / 1 - 2 = ?",
options: ["32", "1", "4", "46"],
answer: "32"
  },
];
export default level20questions;